 <resources>
    <string name="app_name">Assignment#2</string>
     <string name="paragraph">Valentine’s Day, also called St. Valentine’s Day, holiday (February 14) when lovers express their affection with greetings and gifts. Given their similarities, it has been suggested that the holiday has origins in the Roman festival of Lupercalia, held in mid-February. The festival, which celebrated the coming of spring, included fertility rites and the pairing off of women with men by lottery. At the end of the 5th century, Pope Gelasius I forbid the celebration of Lupercalia and is sometimes attributed with replacing it with St. Valentine’s Day, but the true origin of the holiday is vague at best. Valentine’s Day did not come to be celebrated as a day of romance until about the 14th century.Although there were several Christian martyrs named Valentine, the day may have taken its name from a priest who was martyred about 270 CE by the emperor Claudius II Gothicus. According to legend, the priest signed a letter “from your Valentine” to his jailer’s daughter, whom he had befriended and, by some accounts, healed from blindness. Other accounts hold that it was St. Valentine of Terni, a bishop, for whom the holiday was named, though it is possible the two saints were actually one person. Another common legend states that St. Valentine defied the emperor’s orders and secretly married couples to spare the husbands from war.It is for this reason that his feast day is associated with love.Formal messages, or valentines, appeared in the 1500s, and by the late 1700s commercially printed cards were being used. The first commercial valentines in the United States were printed in the mid-1800s. Valentines commonly depict Cupid, the Roman god of love, along with hearts, traditionally the seat of emotion. Because it was thought that the avian mating season begins in mid-February, birds also became a symbol of the day. Traditional gifts include candy and flowers, particularly red roses, a symbol of beauty and love.</string>
     <string name="paragraph2">The role of husband and wife are clearly defined so that each knows what is expected of them. Islam views marriage as an equal partnership between two people, by which they can gain Allah’s pleasure through mutual cooperation, trust, respect and faithfulness. If you adhere to the following guidelines laid down by Allah, you will be able to enjoy a successful partnership.

Each partner in the marriage has been assigned a particular role. Allah says in the Holy Qur’an:
“He said, our Lord is He Who gave unto everything its proper form and then guided it to its proper function.” (20:51)

Accordingly, man has been assigned to working outside the home as the breadwinner because of his greater physical strength and psychological abilities; likewise woman is physiologically and emotionally suited to bearing children and has been made responsible for their upbringing and maintaining the home.

To ensure the smooth running of the partnership, one partner has been put in charge. Allah has appointed the husband to act as a “guardian” over his wife (see Holy Qur’an, 4:35). This does not give him the right to dominate his wife or abuse her in any way. It simply means that he is responsible for her well-being and that he has to spend out of his earnings to maintain the family and the household. In return, his wife is expected to obey him.
Mutual respect and cooperation are essential to producing a good relationship between husband and wife. Allah says:
“They are a garment for you, and you are a garment for them…” (Holy Qur’an, 2:188)

Clothing is worn for protection, adornment and to hide defects. In the same way, man and woman should protect each other’s honor and morals, and make each other feel secure with love, support and understanding. They should keep each other’s secrets and should not air each other’s shortcomings in public.

The Holy Prophet (peace and blessings of Allah be on him) was very concerned about the welfare of women. He constantly advised his followers to treat their wives with kindness. His own conduct with his wives provides the perfect example. Some hadith are:

“The most perfect believer in the matter of faith is he whose behavior is best; and the best of you are those who behave best to their wives.”
“Let no Muslim man entertain any rancor against a Muslim woman. Should he dislike one quality in her, he would find another which is pleasing.”
</string>
</resources>